const easyQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who was the current coach of AS Roma as of the beginning of the 2022/23 season?",
    options: [
      "Carlo Ancelotti",
      "Jose Mourinho",
      "Sean Dyche",
      "Maurizio Sarri",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Jose Mourinho",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What club holds the most Champions League trophies as of the beginning of the 2022/23 season?",
    options: ["Liverpool", "Bayern Munich", "Arsenal FC", "Real Madrid"],
    correctAnswer: "Real Madrid",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What club currently holds the most English Premier League titles?",
    options: [
      "Manchester United",
      "Manchester City",
      "Tottenham",
      "Chelsea FC",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Manchester United",
  },
  {
    question: "What country is Lorenzo Insigne from?",
    options: ["Spain", "Belguim", "Italy", "Croatia"],
    correctAnswer: "Italy",
  },
  {
    question: "What country has the most FIFA World Cups as of 2023?",
    options: ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Germany", "France"],
    correctAnswer: "Brazil",
  },
  {
    question: "Erling Braut Haaland is from what country?",
    options: ["Bosnia and Herzegonia", "Norway", "Cyprus", "Wales"],
    correctAnswer: "Norway",
  },
  {
    question: "Fulham FC is a football club located in what city in the UK?",
    options: ["London", "Leeds", "Liverpool", "Birmingham"],
    correctAnswer: "London",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What season did Sergio Aguero scored THAT goal to win the league for Man. City on the last day of the season?",
    options: ["2008/2009", "2013/2014", "2010/2011", "2011/2012"],
    correctAnswer: "2011/2012",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What Club did Frank Lampard move to after leaving Chelsea in 2014?",
    options: ["LA Galaxy", "Wrexham FC", "Man. City", "West Ham"],
    correctAnswer: "Man. City",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the African Cup of Nations in 2013?",
    options: ["Nigeria", "Ivory Coast", "Senegal", "Cameroon"],
    correctAnswer: "Nigeria",
  },
  {
    question: `Who is Barcelona's record goal-scorer as of 2023?`,
    options: ["Luis Suarez", "Lionel Messi", "Ronald Koeman", "Ronaldinho"],
    correctAnswer: "Lionel Messi",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the 2018 World cup?",
    options: ["France", "Germany", "Spain", "Brazil"],
    correctAnswer: "France",
  },
  {
    question: `What was the name of Leicester City's Manager during their EPL triumph in 2015/16?`,
    options: ["Marco Silva", "Roy Hodgson", "Sean Dyche", "Claudio Ranieri"],
    correctAnswer: "Claudio Ranieri",
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the last Serie A player to win the Balon D'Or?`,
    options: [
      "Fabio Cannavaro",
      "Francesco Totti",
      "Kaka",
      "Andriy Shevchenko",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Kaka",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for most goals at the FIFA World Cup with 16 goals?",
    options: [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Just Fontaine",
      "Ronaldo Nazario",
      "Miroslav Klose",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Miroslav Klose",
  },
  {
    question: "What team won the 2012 Fifa Club World Cup?",
    options: ["Chelsea", "Corinthians", "Al Ahly", "Bayern Munich"],
    correctAnswer: "Corinthians",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the English team that holds the record for least goals conceded in a league season with 15?",
    options: ["Manchester City", "Liverpool", "Chelsea FC", "Arsenal"],
    correctAnswer: "Chelsea FC",
  },
  {
    question: `The name of the player with the most Balon D'or awards is?`,
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Marco Van Basten",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Roberto Baggio",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lionel Messi",
  },
  {
    question: `What country is the club 'Rennes' in?`,
    options: ["Scotland", "England", "Portugal", "France"],
    correctAnswer: "France",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who has the most goals in the UEFA Champions League with 140 goals?",
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Robert Lewandoski",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Karim Benzema",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
  },
];

//......................................................................................

const midQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who wore no. 28 for Leicester city during the 15/16 season where they won the title?",
    options: [
      "Christian Fuchs",
      "Ngolo Kante",
      "Wes Morgan",
      "Danny Drinkwater",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Christian Fuchs",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who won the Golden ball for the 2010 FIFA World Cup held in south Africa?",
    options: [
      "David Villa",
      "Wesley Sneijder",
      "Diego Forlan",
      "Andres Iniesta",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Diego Forlan",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the only club to win a sextuple within a calender year this century?",
    options: ["Barcelona", "Real Madrid", "Bayern Munich", "Ajax"],
    correctAnswer: "Barcelona",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The only team to experience a 9-0 loss twice in the premier league is...?",
    options: [
      "Middlesbrough",
      "Southampton",
      "Derby County",
      "Nottingham Forest",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Southampton",
  },
  {
    question: `In the 1986 world cup, what country did Diego Maradona score his famous 'Hand of God' against?`,
    options: ["Brazil", "Argentina", "England", "France"],
    correctAnswer: "England",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What nation won the very first edition of the world cup back in 1930?",
    options: ["Uruguay", "Argentina", "Brazil", "Germany"],
    correctAnswer: "Uruguay",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What was the name of the manager that lead chelsea to UCL triumph in 2012?",
    options: [
      "Guus Hiddink",
      "Rafa Benitez",
      "Roberto Di Matteo",
      "Carlo Ancelotti",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Roberto Di Matteo",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who scored the only Dortmund goal during the 12/13 UCL Final against Bayern Munich?",
    options: [
      "Matt Hummels",
      "Robert Lewandoski",
      "Marco Reus",
      "Ilkay Gundogan",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Ilkay Gundogan",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the record European Cup winner?",
    options: [
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Paulo Maldini",
      "Paco Gento",
      "Alfredo Di Stefano",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Paco Gento",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I lost the Champions league final with both Bayer Leverkusen and Chelsea. Who am I?",
    options: [
      "Belleti",
      "Ricardo Carvalho",
      "Micheal Ballack",
      "Didier Drogba",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Micheal Ballack",
  },
  {
    question: `Before joining Manchester Unted in 1986, what club did Sir. Alex Ferguson coach prior?`,
    options: ["Aston Villa", "Celtic FC", "Rangers", "Aberdeen"],
    correctAnswer: "Aberdeen",
  },
  {
    question: `In Argentina's 2-0 win over mexico in 2022, Lionel Messi scored the first goal. Who scored the second?`,
    options: [
      "Julian Alvarez",
      "Enzo Fernandez",
      "Alexis McAllister",
      "Angel Di Maria",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Enzo Fernandez",
  },
  {
    question: `Arsenal's Arshavin popularly scored 4 goals against which club in the 08/09 EPL season?`,
    options: ["Aston Villa", "Liverpool FC", "Chelsea FC", "Portsmouth FC"],
    correctAnswer: "Liverpool FC",
  },
  {
    question: `Kylian Mbappe is PSG's record top scorer of all time. Who is in third place(as of 2023)?`,
    options: [
      "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
      "Edinson Cavani",
      "Blaise Matuidi",
      "Pauleta",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the only player to in the Balon D'or while playing for Liverpool?`,
    options: ["Ian Rush", "Jaime Carragher", "Bob Paisley", "Micheal Owen"],
    correctAnswer: "Micheal Owen",
  },
];

//.........................................................................................................
const hardQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "Who scored the winning goal in the 1998 FIFA World cup Quarter-Final between the Netherlands and Argentina?",
    options: [
      "Patrick Kluivert",
      "Batiusta",
      "Dennis Bergkamp",
      "Claudio Lopez",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Dennis Bergkamp",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In the 1995/1996 EPL season, Newcastle and Liverpool played a classic with the score ending 4-3. Who scored the fourth goal in that game?",
    options: ["Stan Collymore", "Ginola", "Les Ferdinand", "Robbie Fowler"],
    correctAnswer: "Stan Collymore",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the FIFA President before Joseph Blatter?",
    options: [
      "Gianni Infantino",
      "Stanley Rous",
      "Bayern Munich",
      "Joao Havelange",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Joao Havelange",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Cristiano Ronaldo has the most goals for Portugal, Who is in second place?",
    options: ["Eusebio", "Pauleta", "Luis Figo", "Ricardo Quaresma"],
    correctAnswer: "Pauleta",
  },
  {
    question: `In the 1999 Balon D'or ceremony, who came third place behind Rivaldo and David Beckham?`,
    options: ["Raul", "Luis Figo", "Andriy Shevchenko", "Thierry Henry"],
    correctAnswer: "Andriy Shevchenko",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who were the only team not to lose a single game at the 2010 World Cup??",
    options: ["Spain", "Netherlands", "Germany", "New Zealand"],
    correctAnswer: "New Zealand",
  },
  {
    question: "What city was the FIFA World Cup final in 2006 held?",
    options: ["Berlin", "Moscow", "Munich", "Rio De Janeiro"],
    correctAnswer: "Berlin",
  },
  {
    question: `Who is Nigeria's second highest goal-scorer as of 2023?`,
    options: [
      "Yakubu Aiyegbeni",
      "Rashidi Yekini",
      "Segun Odegbami",
      "Obafemi Martins",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Segun Odegbami",
  },
  {
    question: "Who won AFCON 2015?",
    options: ["Ghana", "Ivory Coast", "Egypt", "Cameroon"],
    correctAnswer: "Ivory Coast",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In 2012, Bayern Munich beat Real Madrid after a penalty shootout. Cristiano Ronaldo and Sergio Ramos missed their penalties. Who was the third person?",
    options: ["Kaka", "Xabi Alonso", "Karim Benzema", "Sami Khedira"],
    correctAnswer: "Kaka",
  },
  {
    question: `Who won the Premier league Golden boot in the 2010/2011 season?`,
    options: [
      "Carlos Tevez",
      "Wayne Rooney",
      "Robin Van Persie",
      "Fernando Torres",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Carlos Tevez",
  },
  {
    question: `'If God had wanted us to play football up in the clouds, He would have put grass up there'. Which Coach said this?`,
    options: [
      "Pep Guardiola",
      "Brian Clough",
      "Johan Cruyff",
      "Bill Shankly",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Brian Clough",
  },
  {
    question: `Arsenal's Arshavin popularly scored 4 goals against which club in the 08/09 EPL season?`,
    options: ["Aston Villa", "Liverpool FC", "Chelsea FC", "Portsmouth FC"],
    correctAnswer: "Liverpool FC",
  },
  {
    question: `Kylian Mbappe is PSG's record top scorer of all time. Who is in third place(as of 2023)?`,
    options: [
      "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
      "Edinson Cavani",
      "Blaise Matuidi",
      "Pauleta",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the only player to in the Balon D'or while playing for Liverpool?`,
    options: ["Ian Rush", "Jaime Carragher", "Bob Paisley", "Micheal Owen"],
    correctAnswer: "Micheal Owen",
  },
];

const totalQuestions = { easyQuestions, midQuestions, hardQuestions };

export default totalQuestions;
